pebly.com 2011-05-28

# Cancer Cove

Welcome to Cancer Cove. Your privacy is important to us and, as described in this Privacy Policy, we have designed our products and services to protect information about you from unauthorized disclosure to others. This policy covers how Cancer Cove treats personal information that Cancer Cove collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Cancer Cove products and services. 

By using our products and services, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and you should visit this page regularly to review any changes. If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at [privacy@allcoves.com](mailto:privacy@Cancer%20Cove.com). 

##  Information Collection and Use 

While using our products and services, you may provide us with personal information directly or via your profile. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable such as name, address, email address, or phone number, etc. Where you have visited our site from certain other sites, such as facebook.com, we may also record your user ID for that site. 

You may also post information, opinions, voting records, text, sounds, photographs, audio, video, images, graphics, and other content or materials of any nature (collectively, "Materials") to our applications via comment boards, discussion boards, online forums, chat, and messaging. You should exercise caution when disclosing any personal information in these areas as any information disclosed in these areas may be automatically made public. You have control of who sees this Material through your use of the privacy setting available through the application. If you choose, the Materials will be viewable by other users. 

The personal information you provide may be used for such purposes as personalizing your visits to our sites, responding to your requests for certain products and services, customizing the advertising and other content you see, notifying you about new features, helping to resolve site problems, handling and/or routing your customer support questions and issues, and informing you of upgrade opportunities, contests, prizes, and/or special events. We may also use such information for the purposes of improving the quality and design of our sites and applications, creating new site features, and analyzing and understanding how our sites and services are used. Your personally identifiable information may be used in a form aggregate with the information of other users and we may provide such aggregate information to our partners to let them know how our users, collectively, use our sites or applications. We do not disclose aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally. 

##  Information Sharing and Disclosure 

As part of our regular business conduct, we may share information with companies or individuals providing services or acting on our behalf, such as companies providing technological or fulfillment services. These third parties have access to your information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. While we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security procedures as Cancer Cove, we will take all reasonable precautions under the circumstances to ensure the protection of your personal information. 

You may opt-in to allow third parties, such as advertisers and nonprofits, to receive the information you provide by checking the appropriate box when you are providing information. If you tell us to share your information with a third party, the third party's use of that information will be governed by their privacy policy, not ours. 

We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the Cancer Cove, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies. 

If the ownership of all or substantially all of Cancer Cove, business, or substantial portions of the business owned by Cancer Cove, were to change, your information may be transferred to the new owner so the new owner can continue providing services to you. In any such case, your information would remain subject to the protections provided in our Privacy Policy. 

Please remember that anyone who has access to your username and password may be able to access your personal information; therefore, we encourage you to keep your password secret to prevent any unwanted access. 

##  Child Protection 

Cancer Cove does not offer its products and services to, or knowingly collect or solicit information from, anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, do not provide us with any information. Any information we receive from people we believe to be under 13 will be purged from our database. 

##  Third-Party Advertising Companies 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our applications. Cancer Cove does not provide any Personally Identifiable Information to third-party advertising companies. Note, however, that if an advertiser asks Cancer Cove to show an advertisement to users with certain characteristics (for example, women ages 18-24) or a segment of that group (for example, women ages 18-24 who have viewed certain categories of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the third-party advertising company may conclude that you have the characteristics of the audience that they are trying to reach. 

##  Links 

Cancer Cove may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site. 

##  Contacting Us 

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at [privacy@allcoves.com](mailto:privacy@allcoves.com)
